Guide to the Henry S. Kaplan Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Notebooks, Series 2
  - Notebook on Novo Research Seminar (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - B/W photos (6); CBRL Dedication 10-4-75 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - B/W photo (1); Framed; Cancer cells (?) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Grant Apps., CA 10372-13 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Grant Application, Studies of Retrovirus, CA 29079-01 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Putative Human Lymphoma, C-type Virus Studies (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Contract CP4 NOI CP9-1044 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - NOI - CP 43228 Progress Reports (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - NCI Grant Application May, 1982; Mechanisms of Induction-Murine T Cell (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - GK103b
    - Grant Proposal: Heteromyelomas for Human Monoclonal Antibody Production (Box 17 (16), Folder 1)
    - Lymphoma Program Project Grant (Box 17 (16), Folder 2)
    - Grant CA-05838-20 Project: Radiation Immunosuppression and Transplantation Tolerance (Box 17 (16), Folder 3)
    - Biological Aspects of Carcinogenesis by Radiation. CA-03352 Grant Project (Box 17 (16), Folder 4)
    - Grant Application CA-29876: Human Hybridoma Antibodies in Neoplastic Disease (Box 17 (16), Folder 5)
    - Use of TLI in Renal Transplantation: Grant AM30029-02 (Box 17 (16), Folder 6)
    - Use of TLI in Rheumatoid Arthritis: Grant Application (Box 17 (16), Folder 7)
    - Use of TLI in Lupus Nephritis: Grant Application (Box 17 (16), Folder 8)
- Teaching Materials, Series 3
  - Additional Class Material for HB 154 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Teaching Human Biology 154 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Other Courses and Teaching Materials (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Human Rights and Israel activities, Series 4
  - N.E. Asia - U.S. Forum. Dr. John Lewis (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - China File (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Human Rights - Argentina (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Human Rights - Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences; Committee on Human Rights (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Human Rights - U.S.S.R. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Cancer Biology Committee (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - CA Bio Applications (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Other Related Israel Foundations (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Hebrew Univ. Hadassah Medical Center: Sharett Institute of Oncology (Fuks, Mann, Penchas) (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Weizman Institute: Brochures, Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Weizman Institute: Scientific Advisory Council of American Committee (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Israel Cancer Research Fund - 1982 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - ICRF Current Applications & Recipients (Box 18, Folder 9)
- HODGKIN'S DISEASE Manuscript, 2nd edition, Series 5
  - Preface, Chapter one (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chapter two (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Chapter three (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Chapter four (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chapter five (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Chapter six (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Chapter seven (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Chapter eight (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Chapter nine (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Chapter ten (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Chapter eleven (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Chapter eleven (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Chapter eleven (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Chapter twelve (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Chapter thirteen (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bibliography (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - HODKIN'S DISEASE, 2nd Ed., book (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Progress Report for Research Programs Contracts (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Biology of Cancer (Folder Empty) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Radiation Therapy, General and Reviews (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Radiation Therapy and Specific Neoplasms (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Hodgkin's Disease; Prognosis, Relapse, Reviews (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Megavoltage and Pi Meson; Development and Studies (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Hodgkins Disease; Treatment and Clinical Trials (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Hodgkins Disease; Diagnosis, Clinical Manifestations and Staging (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Tissue Injury, Complications of RX (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Non-Hodgkins Lymphomas, Diagnosis, Clinical (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Non-Hodgkins Lymphomas, Treatment, Clinical Trials (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Non-Hodgkins Lymphomas, Prognosis, Relapse-Reviews (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Hodgkins Disease, Immunology (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Human Hybridomas and Monoclonal Antibodies (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Biology of Human Lymphomas (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Viral Isolates from Human Lymphoma Cell Lines (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Exper. Specific Immunotheraphy (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Leukemia, Exper.-Reviews (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Leukemia, Exper.-Virus Studies (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Leukemia, Target Cell Studies (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Leukemia, Role of Thymus (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Leukemia, Exper.-Radiation, Shielding, and Marrow studies (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Leukemia, Immunologic Aspects (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Leukemia, Hormonal and Constitutional Factors (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Leukemia, - Biochemical studies (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - In viro Culture of Exper. Lymphomas (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Molecular Radiobiology DNA Injury and Repair (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cell and Tumor Radiobiology (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Radiosensitizers (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lymphoid Tissue - Radiation Effects (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Radiation Lethality Studies (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Graft vs. Host Disease (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Abstract Files, Series 6
  - A083 - Department of Radiology
    - 3 x 5 cards: Clinical Abstract File. Emphasis on clinical areas: bone tumors, breast carcinoma, radiation protection, radiation injury (Box 18)
  - SECTIONS
    - Adrenal Tumors (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Anemia, Pernicious (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Anus, Malig. Tumors (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Betatilon (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Bladder, Malig. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bone Tumors (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Brain Tumors (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Breast Carcinoma: General, Reviews (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Breast Carcinoma: Etiology and Pathogenesis (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Breast Carcinoma: Diagnosis (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Breast Carcinoma: Familiar & Genetic (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Breast Carcinoma: Hormone and Metabolism (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Breast Carcinoma: Routes of Metastasis (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Breast Carcinoma: Radiotherapy (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Breast Carcinoma: Surgical Procedures (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Breast Carcinoma: Castration (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Breast Carcinoma: Hormone RX (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Breast Carcinoma: Adjuyant RX (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Breast Carcinoma: Chemotherapy (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Breast Carcinoma: Adrenalectomy (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Breast Carcinoma: Immunotherapy (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Breast Carcinoma: Immunology (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Breast Carcinoma: Recurrent (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Breast Carcinoma: Results & Statistics (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Breast Carcinoma: Leukemia (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Breast Carcinoma: Benign Tumors (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Enviromental Carcinogens (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Occupational Cancer (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Cancer - Economic Costs (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Cancer - Psychsocial Aspects (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Cancer - Epidemiology (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Cancer - Clinical Trials (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Cancer - Immunodiagnosis (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Cancer - Immunotherapy, Clinical (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Cancer - Immune Response vs Prognosis (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Cancer in immunologic deficiency & suppression (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Cancer induced by drugs & hormones (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Cancer - Prognosis (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Cancer - Diagnosis & Control (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Cancer - Lymphangiography (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Cytology, Exfoliative, in cancer DX, Gen (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Cancer: Treatment (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Cancer: Research (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Cancer: Quack Remedies (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Cervex - Carcinoma (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Cervix - Carcinoma, Cytology & Histogenesis (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Cervix - Carcinoma: During Pregnancy (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Cervix - Carcinoma: Etiology & Epidemiology (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Cervix - Carcinoma: Clin. Diagnosis & Staging (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Cervix - Carcinoma: Lymphnode Metastases (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Cervix - Carcinoma: Results & Statistics (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Cervix - Carcinoma: Causes of Death, Autopsy Data (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Cervix - Carcinoma: Radiation RX (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Cervix - Carcinoma: Radiation, Interstitial (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Cervix - Carcinoma: Rad., Transvaginal (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Cervix - Carcinoma: Radium, intracavitary (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Chaoul Therapy (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Cervix - Carcinoma: Complications of RX (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Cervix - Carcinoma: Surgical Procedures (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Cervix - Carcinoma: Recurrent & Stump (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Cervix - Carcinoma: Hormone Treatment (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Chemotherapy of Cancer: General & Reviews (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Chemotheraphy of Cancer: Perfusion (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Chemotheraphy of Cancer: Carcinogenic effects (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Chemotheraphy of Cancer: Folic Acids & Antagonists (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Chemo RX - Ackylating Agents (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Chemotheraphy - Hydroxyurea (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Chemotheraphy: Amino Acridines (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Methyl Hydrazine (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Chemotheraphy: Furine Analogs (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Chemotheraphy: Antibiotics (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Chemotheraphy: Fluorinated Pyrimidines (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Chemotheraphy: Chloro-, Bromo-, Iodo-, Pyrimidines (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Chemotheraphy: (non-Halogens) Other Pyrimidines (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Chemotheraphy: Thymine, Thymidine (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Sugar Analogs of the Nucleotides (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Sulfate Analogs of the Nucleotides (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Chemotheraphy: Colchine-like Compounds (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Chemotheraphy: Adrenocortical Hormones (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Chemotheraphy: Deuterium (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Chemotheraphy: Misc. Compounds (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Colon Carcinoma (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Connective Tissue: Malig. Tumors (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Connective Tissue: Kaposi's Disease (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Connective Tissue: Benign Tumors (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Eosinophilic Pneumonia (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Esophagus - Carcinoma (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Eye - Malig. Tumors (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Eye - Misc., Benign Dis., Radiotherapy (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Gall Bladder - Cancer (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Glomus Tumors (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Heart Tumors (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Hemangiomas - PX (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Kaposi's Sarcoma (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Kidney - Malig. Tumors (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Larynx - Carcinoma (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Lip - CA (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Liver - Primary Malig. (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Lung - Inflammatory Dis., Radiotheraphy (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Lung - Primary Cancer (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Lung - Primary Cancer: Etiology, Epidemiology (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - Lung - Primary Cancer: Radiotherapy (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Lung - Primary Cancer: Chemotherapy (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Lung - Primary Cancer: Results & Statistics (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - Lung - Primary Cancer: Surgical Treatment (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - Lymphnode - Metastasis (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - Marrow - Infusion (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - Melanoma (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - Metastasis, Gen. (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Macroglobulinemia (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Myeloma (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - Nasopharynx - Benign (Box 1, Folder 112)
    - Nasopharynx - Malig. (Box 1, Folder 113)
    - Epidemiology (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - HD and HL-A Antigens (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - HD Immunology (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Hyperthermia (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - H.D. Historical (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Radiation RX - Hist. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Exper. "Hodgkins' Like" lesions in mice and rats (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - H.D. Virus & Etiology (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Hypantoin & other Drug Induced Lympha-denopathies (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Infectious Mononucleosis (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Nasal Cavity - Malig. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Neuroblastoma (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Oral Cavity - CA (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Ovary - Malig. Tumors (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Pain, Treatment of (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Pancreas - Carcinoma (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Penis - Cancer (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Pharnyn - Oro, Hypo (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Pituitary, Radiation (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Pituitary, Tumors (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Polycythermia - Venea (?) (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Radiation Injury (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Radiation Injury: Liver (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Radiation Injury: Nervous System (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Radiation Injury: Gastrointestinal Tract (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Radiation Injury: Lung (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Radiation Injury: Endocrine System (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Radiation Injury: Induced Human Malig. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Radiation Injury: Immunology (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Radiation Injury: Cardiovascular (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Radiation Injury: Eyes (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Radiation Injury: Blood (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Radiation Injury: Skeletal System (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Radiation Injury: Skin, Hair (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Radiation Injury: Urinary Tract (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Radiation Protection (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Radiation Physics (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Radiation Sickness (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Radiation Therapy (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Radiation Therapy: Hist. (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Radiation Therapy: Training (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Radiation Therapy: Experimental (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Intra-Operative Radiotherapy (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Interstitial, Isotopic (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Fractionations, Split Course (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Clinical Trials (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Total Dose Studies (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Comb. Surgery, Radiotherapy (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Uterus (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Uterus, Endometriosis (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Vagina, CA (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Vena Cava - Superior Obstruction (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Vulva - CA (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - H.D. General (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Comb. Immunotherapy-Irradiation (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Oxygen Mimics (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - High Pressure Oxygen (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - H2O2 Infusion (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Hypoxia, Anoxia (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Protection - Sulfydryl (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Neutron RX (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Protons (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Electrons RX (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Radionucleides (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Pi-Messons (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - High Let Charged Particles (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Total Bodi - Irradiation (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Tissue Bed Reactions (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Low Dose Rate Protraction (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Radioisotopes (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - TLI in Autoimmune Dis (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - TLI in organ transplant (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Salivary Glands, Tumors (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Sarcoma - Soft Tissue (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Sarcoma - Brotriode (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Sarcoma - Misc. (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Scaly - Ringworm (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Sinuses - CA (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Skin - Benign, Malig. (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Skin - CA (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Stomach Cancer (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Supervoltages (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Testis - Malig. tumors (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Thymus - Tumors (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Thyroid - Benign (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Thyroid - Cancer (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Tongue - CA (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Tonsil - CA (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Ultrasound Scanning (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Uterus Corpus - CA (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Radiosensitizers (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Hodgkins Disease (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - AO 83
      - Cytology (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Chromosone Studies (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - H.D. Lab Diag. - Blood Chemistry (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Lab DX - Blood Cell Counts. (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - H.D. Isotopic (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - RX Lymphangic (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Lab - Surgical Diagnosis Laparotomy (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - H.D. Clinical Staging Classifications (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Complications of Hodgkins Disease (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Assoc. Infection (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - H.D. Misc. Clin. Manifestations (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - H.D. Assoc. Clin Condranns (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Liver spleen (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Lung Plura-Chest wall (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - H.D. Skin (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Bone Marrow (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - H.D. Bone (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Mediastinus (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - H.D. CNS (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - H. D. Heart (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - H. D. Sinuses (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - H. D. Breast (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - H. D. Thyroid (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - H. D. G-U Tract (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - H. D. Thymus (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - H. D. Misc. Localizations (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - H. D. Children (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - H. D. Old Age (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - H. D. Pregnancy (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - H. D. Clinical Symptoms (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - H. D. Alcohol Intolerance (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - H. D. Untreated (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Prognosis Relapse (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Radiotheraphy (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - Radio., RX (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Pallitative Rad. Rx (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Au 198, 189 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Endolymphatic Theraphy (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Chemotherapy (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Comb. Chemotheraphy (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Comb. Modality & Clinical (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Complication of Treatment (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Leukemia and other cancers (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - Radical Surgery (Box 3, Folder 44)
      - Symptomatic & Supportive RX (Box 3, Folder 45)
      - Immuno RX Thymus grafts (Box 3, Folder 46)
      - H. D. Case Histories (Box 3, Folder 47)
      - Leukemia (Box 3, Folder 48)
      - Leukemia Biology (Box 3, Folder 49)
      - Leukemia History (Box 3, Folder 50)
      - Leukemia Cytology (Box 3, Folder 51)
      - Leukemia: Lymphosarcoma Etology (Box 3, Folder 52)
      - Leukemia: Lymphosarcoma Ediolmiologic Factors (Box 3, Folder 53)
      - Leukemia: Etoil Radiation (Box 3, Folder 54)
      - H. D. Pathology (Box 3, Folder 55)
      - Leukemia, Etiology (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Leukemia, Etiology Drug Reactions (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Human Occupational (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Leukemias - Pathogenesis (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Leukemias Etoil Virus (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Leukemias Etoil. - Polythemia (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Leukemias Etoil. - Congenital/Familias (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Leukemias Etoil. - Benzoil (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Leukemias Etoil & Mongolism (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Leukemias Etoil. Misc. (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Leukemia: Clinical Aspects (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Splenectomy (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Leukemias - Immunology (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Leukemia - Anemia (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Leukemia - Chemotheraphy (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Leukemia - Radiation (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Leukemia - Immunotherapy (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Leukemia: Survival Procedures (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Leukemia: Marrow Transplants (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Marrow Applasia Transplants (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Lymphomas - General (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Lymphomas - Immunology (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Lymphomas - Epidemilogic (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Lymphomas - Pathology (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - Lymphomas - Electron Microscope, Cytology (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - Leukomia, Lymphoscarcoma, Giant Folicle Type (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Lymphomas - Lab DX (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - Lymphomas - Staging (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Lymphomas - Childhood (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - Lymphomas - Marrow Involv. (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - Lymphomas - CNS (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - Lymphomas - Waldeyer Ring (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - Lymphomas - Thyroid (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - Lymphomas - Bone (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - Lymphomas - Skin (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - Lymphomas - Gonads (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - Lymphomas - Lung, Pleura (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - Lymphomas - GI Tract (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - Lymphomas - Breast (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - Lymphomas - Spleen (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - Lymphomas - G-U Tract (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - Leukemia Lympho Scarcoma: Clinical Manifestations (Box 4, Folder 42)
      - Lymphomas - Clinical Trials (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - Lymphomas - Anepua (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - Lymphosarcoma: Surgical Treatment (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - Lymphomas - Isotope Therapy (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Lymphomas - X Ray Therapy (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Lymphomas - Hormone Therapy (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Lymphomas - Chemotherapy (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - Lymphomas - Combined Modality (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Lymphomas - Immunotherapy (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Lymphomas - Prognosis, Survival (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Lymphomas - Comparisons (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Lymphomas - Marrow Transplantations (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - Leukemia/Lymphoma: Adult T-Cell (Box 4, Folder 55)
      - Lymphoblastic: Lymphoma T-Cell (Box 4, Folder 56)
      - Burkett Lymphoma (Box 4, Folder 57)
      - Mycosis Fungoides (Box 4, Folder 58)
      - Hairy Cell Leukomia (Box 4, Folder 59)
      - Immunoblastic: Lymphadenotherapy (Box 4, Folder 60)
      - Cassette tape (1):
        - Cassette tape (1): Lymphomas & Leukemias. Movie film (1) on Hodgkins Disease. (Box 5)
- Miscellaneous Materials, Series 8
  - Biographical (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Obituaries (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Oral History (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Photographs (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Profession papers of H. Kaplan: curriculum vitae, bibliography, awards, essays concerning Hodgkin's Disease, pathology report. (Box 4)
  - Progress Reports for Research Programs Contracts. (Box 4)
  - Computer Printout: HDPLAG (Box 4)
  - Special Publications of International Journal of Radiation Oncology (Box 4)
  - Pamphlets and articles concerning carcinomas (Box 4)
  - 3x5" index cards from a file cabinet reflecting drawer and tab separators.
    - Drawer Name: Adrenal, General Biochemistry
      Section 1: Adrenal
      - Drawer 1, Tab 1 - Adrenal
      - Drawer 1, Tab 2 - Steroids, Adrex., and Transplantation
      - Drawer 1, Tab 3 - Inflammation: Infection, Immunity
      - Drawer 1, Tab 4 - Lymphoid Tissues, Blood and Marrow
      - Drawer 1, Tab 5 - Steroids in Miscellan. Dis.
      - Drawer 1, Tab 6 - Androgenic
      - Drawer 1, Tab 7 - Steroid Chemistry
      - Drawer 1, Tab 8 - Exper. Tumors
      - Drawer 1, Tab 9 - Steroids in Human Malig. Dis.
      - Drawer 1, Tab 10 - Adrex in Human Malif. Dis.
      - Drawer 1, Tab 11 - Cushing's Syndrome
      - Drawer 1, Tab 12 - Steroids in Clin. Rad. Reactions
      - Drawer 1, Tab 13 - Steroids and Conn. Tissue, Wound Healing
      - Drawer 1, Tab 14 - Eff. of Radiation
      - Drawer 1, Tab 15 - Steroids: Preg., Fetal Development
      - Drawer 1, Tab 16 - Ascorbic Acid, Cholesterol
      - Drawer 1, Tab 17 - Estrogenic and Gonadotrophic Effects
      - Drawer 1, Tab 18 - ACTH and Steroid Assap and Metabolism
      - Drawer 1, Tab 19 - Gen. Adrenal, Cort. Physiology
      - Drawer 1, Tab 20 - Steroids and Vitamins
    - Drawer Name: Adrenal, General Biochemistry, cont.
      Section 2: Biochemistry - Gen.
      - Drawer 1, Tab 1 - Biochemistry
      - Drawer 1, Tab 2 - Aging
      - Drawer 1, Tab 3 - Analytical Methods
      - Drawer 1, Tab 4 - Methods: Preparative, Biological, Misc.
      - Drawer 1, Tab 5 - Carbohydrates; Dextrans, Glycogen, etc.
      - Drawer 1, Tab 6 - Regulatory Mech. - Feedback, Inducers, Repressors
      - Drawer 1, Tab 7 - Protein Kinases